<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

    <title>Uno Zwei Tros Quatter</title>
    <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/rss.xml" rel="self"/>
    <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one"/>
    <updated>2016-05-26T11:40:19+00:00</updated>
    <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one</id>
    

    
    <entry>
        <title>Big Issue</title>
        <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/2016/05/17/big-issue.html"/>
        <updated>2016-05-17T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one1</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A big issue in Switzerland is the cultural value of new born unwanted babies. Switzerland has eight baby hatches. A baby hatch is a safe place where people, usually mothers can anonymously leave their unwanted babies to be cared for by others. A mother has twelve months to reclaim their baby before it is put up for adoption. This is a big issue because it is controversial.  Do we know if the baby is really unwanted by the mother if the father is abandoning the baby at the hatch?  Is the mother consenting? Is she safe, healthy and alive? Could another family member bring the baby up? Does the father know what has happened to his child? It is really needed if only sixteen children have been left at the facility since it opened in 2001. Does it reduce infanticide? What about the rights of the child being able to know who its parents are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/babyhatch.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Baby Hatch, Einsiedeln, Switzerland&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Baby Hatch, Einsiedeln, Switzerland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Australian authorities considered “baby hatches’, after the case of baby Lily Grace, found buried in sand dunes at Sydney’s Maroubra Beach in 2014. To date, Australia does not have a Baby Hatch .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest issue is the life of the baby. The baby needs a loving lifetime family and if this system makes it possible then I am all for the concept being introduced into Australia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
&lt;div class=&quot;quote-with-name&quot;&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Matterhorn Location&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;div id=&quot;map&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
--&gt;

&lt;script&gt;$(&#39;#map&#39;).vectorMap({
    map: &#39;ch_mill&#39;,
    hoverOpacity: 0.7,
    hoverColor: false,
    markerStyle: {
        initial: {
            fill: &#39;#F8E23B&#39;,
            stroke: &#39;#383f47&#39;
        }
    },
    regionStyle: {
        initial: {
            fill: &quot;#f2e8b6&quot;
        },
        hover: {
            fill: &#39;#e8b84d&#39;
        }
    },
    backgroundColor: &#39;rgba(252, 251, 248, 0.75)&#39;,
    markers:  [
        {latLng: [45.976389, 7.658333], name: &#39;Matterhorn&#39;}
    ]
});
&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Arrival in Utopia</title>
        <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/2016/05/09/shock-confuse.html"/>
        <updated>2016-05-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one1</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As pointed out on &lt;a href=&quot;http://expatarrivals.com&quot;&gt;expatarrivals.com&lt;/a&gt;, Switzerland can be a stark contrast to some of it’s neighbours. Even before you arrive in a major town you begin to get a sense of how orderly and clean everything is. They give the example of a train trip from from Milan to the Italian canton, Ticino. A trip that starts off travelling through some what coarse Italian landscape passing town after town with partially neglected stations with buildings that are in need of much love, or even jut a fresh coat of paint.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/trainstation.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Täsch station, Switzerland near the Matterhorn&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Täsch station, Switzerland near the Matterhorn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Then you reach the Swiss border, where you are immediately met with well maintained and looked after clean stations. What a Utopia!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However this Utopia comes with a cost, a literal cost. Another culture shock that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.culture-shock.me/story/77669&quot;&gt;many&lt;/a&gt; experience is the high cost of everything. As &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.culture-shock.me/story/77669&quot;&gt;Florent&lt;/a&gt; notices you can learn a lot about a place even from it’s airport. Consider Hong Kong or Singapore’s airport, instant fast reliable free wifi covers the every metre. This contrasts with Zurich’s airport where slow costly and timed internet lets you know just how expensive your adventure is going to be. “nothing is free in Switzerland!” &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.culture-shock.me/story/77669&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Florent&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Assess - Xtreme Environmental Issues</title>
        <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/2016/04/03/international.html"/>
        <updated>2016-04-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one1</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;international-engagement&quot;&gt;International Engagement&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Switzerland is heavily involved with many international organisation. It hosts numerous international headquarters such as: CERN - European Organisation for Nuclear Research, WHO - World Health Organisation, GAIN - Global alliance for improved Nutrition or the one I’ll be talking about UNEP United Nations Environment Programme.
UNEP is the global authority on the environment. As someone who is studying Computer Science, I can see a world of ways in which technology is key to helping solve and diagnose some of the worlds environmental issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The European headquarters of the United Nations Environment Programme (UNEP) is based in Geneva, Switzerland. This organisation is charged with the responsibility to find global solutions and strategies for the extreme threat of climate change. UNEP collects ans synthesizes environmental data from many organisations across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LDBFA3L4aos&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My specific disciplinary skills are in software development, these skills are extremely valuable to an organisation that collects processes and interprets such huge volumes of data.
There are many areas of focus within UNEP, including climate change, disasters and conflicts, eco-system management and environmental governance. An example of where these skills are already being used is “&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.madingleymodel.org/&quot;&gt;The Madingley Model&lt;/a&gt;”, which is a partnership between UNEP and Microsoft to develop a general ecosystem model, a model that simulates all life on Earth. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.madingleymodel.org/&quot;&gt;www.madingleymodel.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/YDKrXmcGoSo&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Madingly Model is particularly important as humans put more pressure on Earth’s ecosystems, as we need a way of determining what our impact will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I became aware of UNEP’s work in Switzerland, though Microsoft’s involvement. Microsoft also has a research center at the University of Melbourne, where I’m studying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
Switzerland is heavily involved with many international organisation. It hosts numerous international headquarters such as: CERN - European Organisation for Nuclear Research, WHO - World Health Organisation, GAIN - Global alliance for improved Nutrition or the one I&#39;ll be talking about UNEP United Nations Environment Programme.
UNEP is the global authority on the environment. As someone who is studying Computer Science, I can see a world of ways in which technology is key to helping solve and diagnose some of the worlds environmental issue. 
Can you identify a situation or an issue for meaningful international engagement in your country specialisation?

Describe the process by which you might identify a situation or an issue for meaningful international engagement in your country specialisation and how you could find out whether your particular disciplinary skills could contribute to improving that situation or issue.

Some points to think about:

the individuals, communities and/or authorities to consult 
your particular disciplinary skills
how/whether your skills can be adapted to different needs
the people or skills you would need to work with to bring about meaningful international engagement in your country specialisation
In your blogpost, you will need to:

explain the process by which you might identify the situation or issue
describe your contribution to the situation or issue and/or cooperation with other people possessing complementary skills
articulate how your approach constitutes meaningful international engagement



Switzerland is one of the wealthiest countries, with a high quality of life, it has four official languages (French, German, Italian, and Romansh), is prominent a member of the United Nations and has a motto *&quot;Unus pro omnibus, omnes pro uno&quot;* or in English *&quot;One for all, all for one&quot;*. Not only is Switzerland an International nation with four diverse languages, Switzerland is host to numerous international headquarters such as: CERN - European Organisation for Nuclear Research, WHO - World Health Organisation or GAIN - Global alliance for improved Nutrition.
Despite all this, the Swiss government seems reluctant to grow their diversity and help host refugees.  
Since the 1990&#39;s Swiss Asylum Law has required Asylum Seekers to contribute to the costs of hosting them. By law the country is permitted to confiscate assets from those seeking asylum. They are allowed to confiscate up to 1,000 Swiss francs (~ US$995 or ~ €913 euros).
   
{::nomarkdown}&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/languages.gif&#39; alt=&#39;Language groups of Switzerland&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Language groups of Switzerland&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;{:/nomarkdown}
As [*SwissInfo.ch*](http://www.swissinfo.ch/) puts it _&quot;For some, Asylum Seekers are a drain on the economy and a threat to social stability; For others, helping them is a cornerstone of Switzerland’s humanitarian tradition&quot;_ 

Compared to other nations in Europe, Switzerland is in a position where it can help. Recently the racism commission has been highly critical of the Swiss Government and the opposition in the lead up to the  federal election.  What&#39;s particularly interesting is how the Swiss feel. News media reports carried the results of a survey showed that just under half think the country should close its borders, at least temporarily, but yet most Swiss still feel it’s important to continue helping some of the hundreds of thousands of refugees trying to reach Western Europe through the Mediterranean. –   ([Source](http://www.swissinfo.ch/directdemocracy/hate-speech_racism-commission-sees-risks-ahead-of-federal-elections/41633822)).

As someone who is studying Computer Science, I see potential engaging ways of informing others about this issue. Such as through the use of visualisations.
 
 --&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Essentialism</title>
        <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/2016/03/31/essentialism.html"/>
        <updated>2016-03-31T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one1</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As I have talked about &lt;a href=&quot;/2016/03/08/symbols.html&quot;&gt;earlier&lt;/a&gt;, when you ask people to think of Switzerland many items can come to mind. I have found it interesting to better investigate the common ideas relating to Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To help get a more general idea of how other people perceive Switzerland I decided to perform and experiment.  I decided to Google &lt;em&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com.au/search?q=switzerland&quot;&gt;Switzerland&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/em&gt; and then also &lt;em&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com.au/search?q=visit%20switzerland&quot;&gt;visit Switzerland&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The text results highlighted a few key things. 
Many of the results were about travelling upon a budgeting. Giving the indication of just how expensive Switzerland is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of the image results showed beautiful scenery with huge impressive mountains in the background and often a perfectly blue lake in the foreground.&lt;br /&gt;
For me a surprising number of the shots showed Swiss railways.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/VisitSwitzerland.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;&quot;Visit Switzerland&quot; Image results&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&quot;Visit Switzerland&quot; Image results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;however-how-accurate-is-this-representation&quot;&gt;However how accurate is this representation?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;is-switzerland-as-expensive-as-it-is-made-out-to-be&quot;&gt;Is Switzerland as expensive as it is made out to be?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Average hotel price certainly indicates it is one of the most expensive.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/hotel.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Hotel Prices&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hotel Prices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;does-switzerland-have-countless-beautiful-mountains&quot;&gt;Does Switzerland have countless beautiful mountains?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Union Internationale des Associations d’Alpinisme, yes. Switzerland has over 4400 summits taller than 2000m. Are they all beautiful? I certainly think so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
This question responds to ideas from the Week 5 lecture and reading. You should prepare your post before your Week 5 tutorial. 

# How has your country specialisation been essentialised? 

Find an &#39;essence&#39; affixed to your country, or a misrepresentation or stereotype about it. 

You can find anything you like (and that suits your blog angle). You might choose, for example:

Tourism marketing videos or guidebooks
Outsiders&#39; perspectives on the place
An earlier post where you have yourself essentialised the country
In your blogpost, you will need to:

Explain what the essence/misrepresentation is
Show how it might be challenged
Critically consider why place essentialism is problematic in this context
--&gt;
&lt;!--
&lt;div class=&quot;quote-with-name&quot;&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Matterhorn Location&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;div id=&quot;map&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
--&gt;

&lt;script&gt;$(&#39;#map&#39;).vectorMap({
    map: &#39;ch_mill&#39;,
    hoverOpacity: 0.7,
    hoverColor: false,
    markerStyle: {
        initial: {
            fill: &#39;#F8E23B&#39;,
            stroke: &#39;#383f47&#39;
        }
    },
    regionStyle: {
        initial: {
            fill: &quot;#f2e8b6&quot;
        },
        hover: {
            fill: &#39;#e8b84d&#39;
        }
    },
    backgroundColor: &#39;rgba(252, 251, 248, 0.75)&#39;,
    markers:  [
        {latLng: [45.976389, 7.658333], name: &#39;Matterhorn&#39;}
    ]
});
&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Assess - Harald Naegeli +  the story of Swiss Street Art</title>
        <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/2016/03/20/street-art.html"/>
        <updated>2016-03-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one3</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Like in lots of places Swiss Street Art, was not seen in the same light as it is today.
One of the &lt;em&gt;fathers&lt;/em&gt; of Swiss street art would have to be &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.graffiti.org/zurich/naegeli.html&quot;&gt;Harald Naegeli&lt;/a&gt; (b. 1939). Harald, started painting &lt;em&gt;“wire frame”&lt;/em&gt; works throughout the city of Zurich, which despite being simple drawings, stood out from the bleak concrete walls earning him the name &lt;em&gt;“Sprayer of Zurich”&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.graffiti.org/zurich/naegeli.html&quot;&gt;(source)&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/undine.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Harald Naegeli&#39;s Undine (1978)&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harald Naegeli&#39;s Undine (1978)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Harald work wasn’t appreciated by many, including the Swiss authorities and was apprehended in June ‘79, after he returned to one of his works after leaving his glasses there.
Before his court case he fled to Germany where he continued his work. He was eventually and reluctantly extradited by Germany after he tried to flee to Denmark and served his jail sentence. During this time a petition was set up to free him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now days, his work is regarded by many as great art in both Germany and Switzerland.
The authorities have restored many of his surviving works. Converting it from an unofficial to and official tourist attraction.
So much so that when the building (University of Zurich) where Undine (seen above) was painted upon was renovated. The work was considered sufficiently valuable to cover it and protect int throughout the works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naegeli’s graffiti represents a political statement against the increasing anonymity in the city of Zurich. Naegeli was invited to spray paint his work in Germany by the Mayor of Osnabruck but he decided not to because he “didn’t work on commission.”&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <title>Assess - Swiss Alps</title>
        <link href="https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one/2016/03/08/symbols.html"/>
        <updated>2016-03-08T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
        <id>https://Uno-Zwei-Tros-Quatter.jamesst.one1</id>
        <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;symbols&quot;&gt;Symbols&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked &lt;em&gt;“what is uniquely Swiss?”&lt;/em&gt; The first symbol many would conjour, is the Swiss Alps, this is likely because most other Swiss symbols can be linked back to the Alps.&lt;br /&gt;
No matter what symbol you picture, it can somehow be related back to the mountains. Take Swiss chocolate, one of the most exported brands from Switzerland is Toblerone. Toblerone not only has their chocolate shaped like a mountain, their logo literally is the Matterhorn.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/0/0b/Toblerone_Bars.jpg/400px-Toblerone_Bars.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Toblerone Bars&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Toblerone Bars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Or consider the Alphorn a musical instrument that’s name literally has &lt;em&gt;“Alp”&lt;/em&gt; in it. The &lt;code&gt;Alp&lt;/code&gt;horn is an instrument that was originally used for communication among Swiss mountain dwellers, now it is also used as an instrument. [&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vfQC-XaNEpM&quot;&gt;Video&lt;/a&gt;]
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;http://img.myswitzerland.com/mys/n49486/images/buehne/alphornblaeser.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Alphorn&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alphorn&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-holder&#39;&gt;&lt;img src=&#39;/img/alps.jpg&#39; alt=&#39;Swiss Alps&#39; /&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;image-caption&#39;&gt;&lt;span class=&#39;ico-photo&#39;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Swiss Alps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#39;text-part&#39;&gt;&lt;p&gt;
The beauty of the mountain range along with the vast array of activities they play host to have made the Swiss Alps, so iconic and symbolic.
Tourism in the Swiss Alps really began in the mid to late 1800’s when many of the mountains were first successfully climbed. With the first successful climbs often being by British Mountaineers along with local guides. Now days they still attract mountaineers, bush walkers, skiers, both cross country and down hill and snowboarders.
For climbers there are a vast array of mountains ranging in difficulty and height.&lt;br /&gt;
For skiers and snowboarders there are over &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_ski_areas_and_resorts_in_Switzerland&quot;&gt;30 ski fields&lt;/a&gt; the biggest of which, the Les Portes du Soleil, having 650km of ski runs, making it a skiers paradise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another side of the Swiss Alps is the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bldgblog.com/2012/06/various-forms-of-lithic-disguise/&quot;&gt;natural fortress&lt;/a&gt; it has provided. 
As described by McPhee in his book, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0374519323/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=bldgblog-20&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0374519323&quot;&gt;La Place de la Concorde Suisse&lt;/a&gt; ,  There are &lt;em&gt;“networks of tunnels, caverns, bunkers, and surface installations, each spread through many tens of square miles”&lt;/em&gt; hidden through the Alps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
&lt;div class=&quot;quote-with-name&quot;&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;Matterhorn Location&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;div id=&quot;map&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
--&gt;

&lt;script&gt;$(&#39;#map&#39;).vectorMap({
    map: &#39;ch_mill&#39;,
    hoverOpacity: 0.7,
    hoverColor: false,
    markerStyle: {
        initial: {
            fill: &#39;#F8E23B&#39;,
            stroke: &#39;#383f47&#39;
        }
    },
    regionStyle: {
        initial: {
            fill: &quot;#f2e8b6&quot;
        },
        hover: {
            fill: &#39;#e8b84d&#39;
        }
    },
    backgroundColor: &#39;rgba(252, 251, 248, 0.75)&#39;,
    markers:  [
        {latLng: [45.976389, 7.658333], name: &#39;Matterhorn&#39;}
    ]
});
&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
    </entry>
    

</feed>